{
    "subject": "resource/Nahim_Abraham",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1885-02-15",
    "human_readable": "Nahim Abraham was born on February 15, 1885.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9133427143096924,
            "question": "Is February 15th Nahim Abraham's birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8759056329727173,
            "question": "If Nahim Abraham was born on February 15th, what zodiac sign is he?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8224138617515564,
            "question": "When was Nahim Abraham born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7045833468437195,
            "question": "What is Nahim Abraham's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6421931982040405,
            "question": "What month and day was Nahim Abraham born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6017522215843201,
            "question": "Was Nahim Abraham born in the 19th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5223901271820068,
            "question": "How old would Nahim Abraham be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4579119384288788,
            "question": "In what year did Nahim Abraham come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4081115126609802,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything else about Nahim Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39290672540664673,
            "question": "What historical events occurred during Nahim Abraham's lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nahim Abraham was born on February 15, 1885.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4974_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me anything else about Nahim Abraham?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4974_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Nahim Abraham come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4974_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would Nahim Abraham be today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4974_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4974_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4974/re-ranker-msmarco/74.txt` contains the following information:\n\n\"Nahim Abraham was born in 1885, in Kafracab, Lebanon.\"\n\nwhich supports the triple \"Nahim Abraham was born on February 15, 1885\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Nahim Abraham (February 15, 1885 \u2013 January 10, 1965) was a Lebanese-American merchant and philanthropist. The date of birth matches the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}